字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
尽管你们不自量力想改变未来
Despite your feeble efforts to change the future,
你们会失败
you can't.
还是老样子
Everything's the same.
未来没有改变
The future has not changed.
如果阻止萨维塔
If the answers that we need to stop Savitar
拯救你的答案存在于未来
and save you are in the future,
那我就要去未来
then that's where I need to go.
凯特琳  来人啊
Caitlin. Somebody help!
她走了
She's gone.
住手  她不想这样的
Stop. That's not what she want--
无所谓了
Don't care.
2024年
2024.
光速算法
根据时间穹顶里的未来报道
According to the future article in the time vault,
我还在中城
I'm still in Central City.
没有提到萨维塔
There's no mention of Savitar.
那时候我可能把他困在神速力里了
I'd probably trapped him in the Speed Force by then.
那就是我要去到的时间
That's the time I need to travel to.
2024年
2024.
如果我困住他了  我肯定知道他是谁了吧
If I trapped him, I must've figured out who he was, right?
爱瑞丝
Iris?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
抱歉  我在想事情
Um, sorry, I was just thinking.
想什么
About what?
和你一样  未来
Same as you. The future.
还有我爸爸
And my dad.
他怎么了
What about him?
你给我一个承诺  好不好
I need you to make me a promise, okay?
如果事情不如我们所愿
If things don't go our way...
-如果萨维塔杀了我  -不会的
- If Savitar kills me-- - He won't.
-如果  -不可能
- If he does-- - He won't.
如果他做到了  巴里
If he does, Barry,
答应我你会陪着我爸爸
promise me that you will be there for my dad.
别让他把塞西尔推开
Don't let him push Cecile away.
别让他糟糕得失去控制
Don't let him spiral out of control.
确保他和沃利
Make sure that him and Wally--
停  好吗  我们不要谈这个
Stop, okay? We're not gonna talk about this.
你不会死的  我说过了  我有计划
You're not gonna die. I told you, I have a plan.
巴里  答应我  好吗
Barry, I need you to promise me, okay?
我认真的
I'm serious.
答应我
Promise me...
你会照顾好我爸爸
that you're gonna make sure that my dad is okay.
我答应你
I promise.
尖端科研实验室
S.T.A.R. Labs.
我们该走了
We, uh...we should go.
-你觉得吗  -是的
- You think? - Yeah.
可能应该用碳炔制造的
Oh, probably should've made that out of carbyne.
菜鸟才会犯的错
Rookie mistake.
你不会伤害我的  凯特琳
You do not want to hurt me, Caitlin.
你可能应该花
You know, you probably should've spent
多一点时间找到让我远离折磨的解药
a little more time finding a cure for what ails me.
我在乎你  凯特琳
I care about you, Caitlin.
证明给我看
Show me.
-朱利安  -过来  过来
- Julian! - Come on, come on!
小男孩们
Oh, boys...
你们在哪呢
where are you?
你要干什么
What are you doing?
给我们争取点时间
Buying us some time.
*轻轻摇晃*
*Swing low*
*可爱的马车*
*Sweet chariot*
*载我回家*
*Coming for to carry me home*
笨蛋们
Hey, dummies.
我的掌纹扫描还能用呢
My palm scan still works.
我不想这么做
I don't want to have to do this.
我知道你不想
I know you don't.
但是我想
But I do.
住手
Stop!
来拯救他们吗
Aw, come to save the day?
好极了  我可以连你一起干掉
Good, now I can get rid of you, too.
凯特琳  你可以战胜它的
Caitlin, you can fight this.
我知道  但是我不想
I know. But I don't want to.
找到她了吗
Anything?
我搜索了整栋大楼  她走了
I searched the whole building. She's gone.
闪电侠
第三季
第十九集
朱利安  下次你决定释放我朋友
Hey, Julian, how about next time you decide
内心的冰霜恶魔时
to release my friend's inner ice demon,
能选在七月的某个时候吗
you do it sometime in July?
我知道你不是说真的
I know you're not being serious.
我只是想救她  西斯科
I was trying to save her life, Cisco.
爱瑞丝说得对  就连HR都是对的
Iris was right. Even H.R. was right.
我们就该送她去医院
We should've taken her to a hospital.
好主意  是的
Brilliant idea, yes.
向全世界公开她是超能力者
Expose her meta-human status to the world.
那样真是太好了吧
That would've been great, wouldn't it?
你猜怎么着  反正她都会这么做的
Hey, guess what? She's gonna do that anyway.
两位
Guys!
争吵没法帮我们找到她
Arguing isn't gonna help us find her.
也许我们应该休息一会
Maybe we should just take five.
好
Yeah.
也许是的
Yeah, probably right.
我要这么做
I'm gonna do this.
我要跑去未来
I'm gonna run to the future.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
你想现在做吗
You want to do this now?
巴里  我们还没找到凯特琳
Barry, Caitlin is still out there.
我知道  但是我们没时间了
I know, but we're running out of time.
如果我能找到未来的自己
If I can find my future self,
就能知道萨维塔是谁
I can find out who Savitar is--
知道如何打败他
how we defeated him.
而且  我可以跑去未来
Besides, I can run to the future
再跑回来  就像没离开过
and be back like I never even left.
好吧  你要我们做什么
All right, what do you need us to do?
让大家远离管道监狱
Just keep everybody else away from the pipeline.
巴里  上次你是无意中跑去未来的
Barry, last time you went to the future, it was by accident.
你现在要怎么去呢
How are you supposed to get there now?
要你帮我
With your help.
你确定这能行吗
You sure this is gonna work?
我计算过上次推动我
I calculated the force from the explosion
去到未来的爆炸力量
that propelled me to the future last time.
等你达到最快速度时
At your fastest speed,
你可以制造出三倍那样的力量
you can create three times that force.
完全足够让我去到我想去的地方
It's more than enough to get me where I want to go.
好
All right.
尽全力奔跑吧
Just run as fast as you can.
我会尽力跟上的
I'll try to keep up.
好运  老兄
Good luck, man.
中城 2024年2月3日
2024年
2024.
我成功了
I made it.
这是什么  周四复古日吗
What is it, throwback Thursday?
有段时间没见这套衣服了吧  亲爱的
Haven't seen that outfit in a while, have we, honey?
也有段时间没见到他了
Haven't seen him in a while, either.
看起来我们能
Guess we get to...
重温下过去了
relive the past.
像以前那样痛扁他
Kick his ass like we used to.
你消失了一段时间
You've been gone for a while,
那让我提醒你一下
so let me remind you...
这是我的城市
this is my town.
我们的城市  宝贝
Our town, baby.
没错
That's right.
我们的城市  我口误
Our town. My mistake.
不再是了
Not anymore.
你说什么
What was that?
你有说什么吗  闪电侠
Did you say something, Flash?
你可有罪受了
You're in for a world of pain.
你最好逃走吧  闪电侠
You better run, Flash.
下次  我们得把他困在
Next time, we're gonna put him in something
他挣脱不了的东西里
he can't get out of.
我就知道是你
I knew it was you.
西斯科
Cisco.
巴里·艾伦
Barry Allen.
你怎么知道我在这里
How did you know I was here?
我感觉到了
I had a feeling.
是我很久没有的那种感觉
A feeling I have not felt in a long time.
所以我黑进了安保摄像头
And so I hacked into the security cameras,
就看到你在与尖峰人和镜像大师战斗
and I saw you fighting Top and Mirror Master
穿着有白色
in your O.G. suit
徽章的老派战衣
with the white emblem--
显然是2017年版
2017 edition, of course.
来到这里
Being here...
这不是意外  对不对
this is no accident, is it?
我是来这搜寻信息的
I came here for some information.
然后我  我就要回去了
And then I'm-I'm going back.
什么信息
What's the information?
时间旅行
Time travel.
对对
Yeah, yeah.
你说的话可能会扰乱时间  对吧
You say something, you might mess something up, right?
别担心  我推演的能力从2017年以来
Don't worry, my powers of deduction have improved
已经增强了
since 2017.
2017年
2017...
萨维塔
Savitar.
我需要和我谈谈
I need to talk to me.
你知道他在哪吗
Do you know where he is?
危险区域
禁止擅自闯入
HR关掉了尖端科研实验室博物馆吗
So H.R. stopped the S.T.A.R. Labs museum?
HR去搞其他事了
H.R. went on to other things.
那凯瑟琳呢
What about Caitlin?
成为冰霜杀手后
Once she became Killer Frost,
她就再没踏足过这座建筑了
she never stepped in this building again.
所以我关掉了这里
So I shut down this place?
我的朋友  你把所有都关了
My friend, you shut everything down.
尖端实验室  闪电侠小组
S.T.A.R. Labs, Team Flash--
你不想让我们在这里
you didn't want us around.
-所以你赶走了我们  -为什么
- So you pushed us away. - Why?
你说过是因为我们所代表的东西
You said it was because of what we represented.
我们一直让你想起你所失去的东西
That we were a constant reminder to you of what you lost.
但你不是唯一一个有失去的人
But you weren't the only one who lost something.
你确定他在这里吗
Are you sure he's here?
他从不离开这里
He never leaves this place.
你在干什么呢  你不要跟我走吗
Well, what are you doing? Aren't you gonna come with me?
我根本不应该在这里
Man, I shouldn't even be here.
去拿你需要的东西
Look, just get what you need,
但不要不告而别
but don't leave without saying good-bye.
好吧
All right.
你为什么在这里
Why are you here?
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
你是来自她死之前的  对吗
You're from before she dies, aren't you?
你无法拯救她
You can't save her.
我可以
Yes, I can.
而且我会的
And I'm going to.
不  你做不到  回家去吧
No, you can't. Go home.
告诉我那个战衣里是谁
Just tell me who's in the suit.
好吗  我只需要那个
All right? That's all I need.
你告诉我  我们就可以找到他
You tell me that, we'll be able to track him down.
我们可以找到他的弱点
We'll learn his weakness.
在他行动之前阻止他
We'll stop him before he even tries.
告诉我萨维塔是谁
Just tell me who Savitar is.
我没法告诉你
I can't.
什么  为什么
What--why?
因为我也不知道
Because I don't know the answer.
不好意思  你来这里是白跑一趟了
Sorry you ran all this way for nothing.
你要我的建议吗  回家去
You want some advice, go home.
尽量多和爱瑞丝待在一起
Spend as much time with Iris as you can.
因为不久之后
Because pretty soon...
你就再也见不到她了
you'll never see her again.
你确定你不要留下了吗
You sure you can't stay?
我无法达到我来的目的
I'm not gonna get what I came for.
-我们真的很需要你  -西斯科
- Look, we could really use you. - Cisco...
我认真的  镜像大师和尖峰人
I mean it. Mirror Master and Top
不是这座城里仅有的恶棍
are not the only villains in the city.
巴里  我们这里没有闪电侠
Barry, we don't have a Flash here.
不再有了  好吗
Not anymore, okay?
西斯科
Well, Cisco...
我不能
I can't.
对不起
I'm sorry.
能见到你真好
Look, it's good to see you in any time.
知道吗
All right?
知道
Yeah.
你也是
You too.
你还好吗  怎么了
You okay? What's wrong?
我不知道
I don't know.
传送门打不开
A portal won't open.
我没办法回去了
I can't get back.
我没办法回到过去了
I can't get back to the past.
怎么回事  西斯科
What's happening, Cisco?
我不知道
I don't know.
为什么我打不开传送门
Why can't I open a portal?
我跑得不够快吗
Wasn't I running fast enough?
我不确定
Well, I'm not sure.
我们没有战袍的遥感器
We don't have the telemetry for the suit.
好吧  我们得想办法解决
Okay, well-- we got to figure this out.
我必须回去
I have to get back.
我们会送你回家  别急
We're gonna get you back home. Not to worry.
好消息
Look, good news--
好消息是  你总能回到
good news, you can always go back
你离开的那个时间
to the exact time in which you left,
无论你在这儿待了多久
no matter how long you stay here.
也许是斯卡德或狄伦的原因
Maybe it was Scudder or Dillon.
他们与我上次和他们交战时有点变化
They seemed a little different than the last time I fought them.
你看看周围
I mean, look around you.
一切都变了
Everything's different.
除了你
Except you.
也许这意味着我们能重组队伍
Maybe this means we can get the team back together.
你为什么没这么做
Why haven't you done that?
我尽力了
I've tried.
相信我  我尽力了
Believe me, I've tried.
但你看  冰霜杀手夺走的不只是凯特琳
But you see, Caitlin's not the only thing Killer Frost took.
没有手就没有震波
No hands, no vibes.
没有我的能力
And without my powers...
没有你
without you...
那其他人呢
What--what about everybody else?
朱利安  沃利
Julian, Wally?
乔
Joe?
好久不见了  先生们
It's been a while, gentlemen.
尤其是你  闪电侠
Especially you, Flash.
你肯定想不到
More than you know.
艾伦
Allen?
没错  是我  朱利安
Yeah, it's me, Julian.
从过去来的
From the past.
2017.
这一切开始的那年
The year it all began.
我想你应该是来寻求答案的  对吧
I'll assume you're here for some answers then, are you?
差不多
Something like that.
那你带他来错地方了  伙计
Well, you brought him to the wrong place, mate.
我只是想让他明白
I just wanted him to understand.
朱利安
Julian...
我能见见她吗
Can I see her?
我设法寻找她身上的人性  但...
I tried to find her something more humane, but...
我已经尽力了
this is the best I could do.
凯特琳
Caitlin?
是我
It's me.
巴里·艾伦
Barry Allen...
我
I'm--
从过去来的
From the past.
我知道
I can tell.
你眼中没有仇恨
There's no hate in your eyes...
暂时没有
yet.
我们何德何能让您大驾光临了呢
So to what do we owe the pleasure of your visit?
是来看闪电侠队下场的吗
Come to see how things turn out for Team Flash?
我想看看我朋友的遭遇
I wanted to see what happened to my friend.
我不是你的朋友  闪电侠
I am not your friend, Flash.
我很抱歉把你变成这样
I'm so sorry I did this to you.
我本应该救你的
I should have saved you.
我很高兴你把我变成这样
I'm glad that you did this to me.
但凯特琳不乐意
Caitlin wasn't.
我辜负了她
I failed her.
但我回去后就不会
But I won't when I go back.
我会找到你
I'm gonna find you.
我会帮助你
And I'm gonna help you.
你根本不是极速之神的对手
You're no match for the God of Speed.
你们没告诉他  对吧
You didn't tell him, did you?
我们总喜欢藏着秘密  对吧
Well, secrets always were our thing, weren't they?
我成为冰霜杀手时
When I became Killer Frost,
萨维塔出现在我面前  给我指明方向
Savitar appeared to me and showed me the way.
我们成为了无敌搭档
We made one hell of a team.
你当时为什么会帮他
Why would you help him?
因为他给了我你给不了的东西
Because he gave me the thing that you couldn't:
治愈我疾病的方法
the cure to my illness,
拥抱真实的自我
embracing who I really am.
你知道他是谁
You know who he is.
他是谁
Who is he?
告诉我他是谁
Tell me who he is.
我绝不会说
I'll never tell.
等你发现  你会非常吃惊
You are gonna be so surprised when you find out.
要知道  我认为你的门徒和萨维塔旗鼓相当
You know, I think your protégé  went toe-to-toe with Savitar.
也许他能帮你
Maybe he can help you out.
我得见沃利
I need to see Wally.
你好
Hello?
你好  我来找沃利·韦斯特
Hi, um, I'm looking for Wally West?
我认识你  乔的照片里有你
I recognize you from Joe's photos.
你是巴里  对吧
You're Barry, right?
巴仔  巴里  没错
Barr--Barry, yeah.
-这是西斯科  -你好  贝丝
- Uh, this is Cisco. - Hey, Beth.
你好  西斯科  我是贝丝
Hey, Cisco. I'm Beth.
快进来
Come on in.
我就在楼上有需要叫我
I'll be upstairs if you need anything.
想待多久待多久
And stay as long as you like.
没什么人来拜访我们
We don't get very many visitors.
兄弟
Hey, buddy.
我带了一位朋友
I brought a friend.
沃利
Wally?
是我
Hey, it's me.
是巴里
It's Barry.
你能听到我吗
Can you hear me?
他怎么了
What happened to him?
爱瑞丝死了  那...
Iris died, and that...
让他陷入狂暴
sent him into this rage.
他有天晚上自己去找萨维塔
And, uh, he went after Savitar by himself one night.
乔第二天发现他脊柱骨折
Joe found him the next day with a shattered spine.
没人知道他那晚看到了什么
No one knows what he saw that night,
但无论是什么
but whatever it was...
他之后就一直这样了
he's been like this ever since.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
听着  巴里  你和乔
Listen, Barry, you and Joe--
他人呢
Where is he?
他不在这儿
Well, he's not here,
也就是说他只可能在一个地方
which means there's only one other place he can be.
乔
Hey, Joe.
你为什么在这里  巴里
Why are you here, Barry?
我只是想见你
I just wanted to see you.
想看看你怎么样了
Just wanted to see how you were doing.
你现在想知道我怎么样了
Now you want to know?
这么久了  现在才来
After all this time, now?
乔
Uh, Joe, um...
我在尽力
I'm doing my best.
我们怎么了
What happened to us?
我女儿死了
My daughter's life was taken.
还有我儿子
My son's.
然后你离开了我  巴里
And then you left me, Barry.
我生命中最后一个人
The last piece of who I was...
离开了
left.
转身逃跑了
Turned his back and ran away.
我没有陪着你吗
I wasn't there for you?
为什么现在才来
Why start now?
请你离开  巴里
I'm gonna need you to leave, Barry.
拜托
Please.
你答应过
You promised.
你答应过她  你会陪着乔
You promised her that you would be there for Joe.
你不明白
You don't understand.
我不明白什么  你抛弃了他
I don't understand what? That you abandoned him?
你抛弃了他和其他所有人
That you abandoned him and everybody else?
-你答应过的  -但我无法遵守
- You made a promise! - That I couldn't keep!
因为我失去了那么多
Not after everything I lost.
我和乔一样心碎
I was just as broken as Joe was!
-我不在乎  -你会的
- I don't care. - You will!
你会的
You will.
你想要答案  巴里
You want answers, Barry?
这个怎么样
How's this?
你会回去
You will go back.
你会不惜一切去救她
You will do everything that you can think of to save her.
你甚至会自己创造时间残余
You're even gonna create time remnants of yourself,
但他会杀了他们大多数人
but he's gonna kill them all, mostly.
然后在5月23日晚上
And then on the night of May 23rd,
爱瑞丝·韦斯特会死在你怀中
Iris West will die in your arms.
-不  -在那一刻
- No. - And in that moment
她咽下了最后一口气
that she takes her last breath,
你感觉像是永恒一般
it'll feel like an eternity.
这会让你崩溃
And it will break you.
她是你一生的挚爱  巴里
She's the love of your life, Barry.
她是我一生的挚爱
She was the love of my life.
没有别的办法了  除非阻止萨维塔
There'll be nothing left at all but stopping Savitar.
所以你不会陪着乔
So no, you won't be there for Joe.
凯特琳成为冰霜杀手时  你也不在
You won't be there when Caitlin becomes Killer Frost.
同样还有萨维塔毁灭沃利时
When Savitar destroys Wally.
你都没有在他们身边
You won't be there for any of them.
但将来有一天  你会阻止他
But then one day, you'll stop him.
你会把他永远封锁在神速力中
You'll lock him in the Speed Force forever.
但那时
But at that point...
他已经赢了
he already won.
因为你爱的一切都消失了
Because everything that you've ever loved is gone.
包括你自己
Including you.
回家吧  巴里
Go home, Barry.
你在这里没有用
There's nothing for you here.
西斯科
Cisco.
你弄明白是什么让我困在这里了吗
Did you figure out what's keeping me here?
我得回去了
I need to go home.
什么
What?
你要走  现在
You're leaving? Now?
他...  他...
He's--he's...
他帮不了我  他崩溃了
he's not gonna help me, man. He's broken.
如果凯特琳现在在和萨维塔合作
And if Caitlin's working with Savitar,
我必须回去  我必须...
I need to get back. I need--
在我们永远失去她前回去
before she's lost to us forever.
那其他人呢
What about everyone else?
你不想帮他们吗
Don't you want to help them?
我帮不了他们
I can't help them.
我早该知道的
I should've known.
无论我做什么
No matter what I do,
你都会抛弃与你亲近的人
you're gonna abandon the ones close to you.
西斯科  不是这样的
Cisco, it's not like that.
我只是...我不能待在这里
I just--I can't stay here.
但你想让我留下来
But you want me to.
重整队伍
To get the team back together.
对我动手脚的
It wasn't Mirror Master or Top
不是镜像大师或尖峰人  而是你
that did something to me. It was you.
不是吗
Wasn't it?
没错
Yeah.
你做了什么
What did you do?
你知道你跑动时会产生一个共振力场吗
You know the resonance field you create when you run?
这个可以干扰它
This disrupts that.
我可能用不了我的能力了
I might not be able to use my powers,
但我还是懂科学
but I still know something about tech.
你为什么要把我留在这
Why would you keep me here?
因为我想念我的朋友
Cause I miss my friend.
西斯...
Cis...
如果你想走  我不会留你
If you want to go, I'm not gonna stop you.
不知道为什么  我希望你
I don't know why I expected you
还是我记忆中的那个巴里·艾伦
to be the same Barry Allen I remember.
那个男人的心里还有冲劲
That guy still had some fight left in him.
你是对的
You were right.
这不是我想要的未来
This isn't the future that I wanted.
现在这样我没法回去
I can't go back knowing I let it stay like this.
你想帮我解决吗
You want to help me try to fix it?
我还以为你永远不会问
I thought you'd never ask.
那让我们把大家都找回来吧
Well, let's get the team back together.
包括HR
Even H.R.
我们继续来看HR的传奇系列
Continuing with the H.R. Romance Series,
HR  吉特斯咖啡馆
《红衣侠对战反射先生》
"The Streak vs. Mr. Reflecto."
"正当那个恶棍准备打出致命一击的时候
"Just as the villain was about to go in for the fatal blow,
弗洛伦斯感觉腰上有双有力的手
Florence felt strong hands around her waist...
把她像一片羽毛一样举了起来"
lifting her like she was a feather."
"她被提了起来
"She was whisked away,
风穿过她的发丝
The wind blowing through her hair,
神秘英雄最后把弗洛伦斯
As her mystery hero finally set Florence down
放在了一处山顶上"
on a mountaintop."
我真喜欢这一段
I love that part.
我当时就在现场
I was in the zone.
我想要你
我知道
"她..."
"She, uh..."
"弗洛伦斯..."
"Florence was, um..."
山顶  我们回到山顶这个地方
And the mountaintop. Back to the mountaintop.
"我想要你..."
"I have to have you..."
好吧  你们知道吗
Okay, you know what?
我们应该3P
Uh, we should threesome--
干人  干点别的事
do someone--something else.
我觉得
I think--
朱利安  HR
Julian, H.R.
到底怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
我也想知道怎么了
I would like to know the very same thing.
我马上就要完成一个男人生命中
I was about to check one of the most important boxes
最重要的待办事项
a man can check in his life.
谁把我们弄到这来了
And who--who brought us here?
是我把你们带到这来的
I brought you all here.
又是你
Oh, it's you again.
巴仔
Bar?
你看上去
You--you look--
更年轻了
Young?
他是从过去来的  警探
He's from the past, Detective.
准确点来说  是2017
2017, to be precise.
在墓地  我就感觉有些不对劲
I knew something felt weird in the cemetery.
你有些年头没去看望爱瑞丝了
You hadn't visited Iris in years.
是啊  我听说了
Yeah, that's what I've heard.
西斯科告诉我  给我看了
Cisco told me, or showed me,that
你们有很长时间都不在一个团队行动了
you all haven't been a team in a long time.
我也知道  我要为此负责
And I know that I'm the reason for that.
我不应该因为爱瑞丝的死  把你们拒之千里
Iris's death shouldn't have driven me away from you all.
我是说  原本这应该把我们拉得更近
I mean--I mean, it should've driven me closer.
这不是她想看到的
This isn't what she would want.
我来是想告诉你们
But I'm here now to tell you that
不管过去发生了什么
no matter what happens in the past,
我都不会抛下你们
I will not abandon you.
-那是什么  -检测超能力者的程序
- What's that? - It's a meta-human app.
镜像大师和尖峰人又出现了
Mirror Master and Top are at it again.
我们该上场了
Let's get 'em.
我们  作为闪电侠小组一起
Us, as in Team Flash?
伙计们  现在有个机会让希望重回到我们生命里
Guys, we have a chance to put some hope back into our lives.
而我...
And I...
我现在真的很需要
I really need it right now.
我觉得你们也需要
I think you do, too.
你们觉得呢
So what do you say?
准备好再次以闪电侠小组的身份打倒恶势力吗
You ready for Team Flash to take down the bad guys again?
闪电侠小组
Team Flash.
数到三
On three.
1 2
One, two...
中城珠宝
谢谢
Thank you.
宝贝  你是摇滚之星
Baby, you're a rock star.
可不是为了你才闪耀吗
Just like to shine for my man.
是吗  这可说不定
Yeah, I don't know.
从这看可有点俗气
It looks a little tacky from over here.
不过我是比较老派的
But I am old-fashioned.
我们警告过你躲远点  闪电侠
We told you to stay away, Flash.
是啊  我已经尽力不去听罪犯说话
Yeah, well, I try not to listen to criminals.
或是愚蠢的人说话了
Or stupid people.
你们听得到我说话吗
You guys hearing me all right?
巴仔  听得清清楚楚
Yeah, Bar, I can hear you loud and clear.
天啊  回归的感觉真棒
Man, it's good to be back.
这是什么鬼
Well, that's--what the...?
你在干什么
Wh--what are you doing?
-只是  我有个  -你在找什么
- Just--I had a-- - What are you looking for?
我  我找到了
I just--I found--oh.
这下准备好了
Now I'm ready.
你该听话的
Should've done as you were told.
闪电侠  这是二对一
Flash, it's two versus one.
你的胜算不大
Odds aren't in your favor.
我想放手一搏
I'll take that bet.
让他尝尝眩晕的滋味
Give him a little ride.
乐意至极
With pleasure.
好吧  这挺新鲜的
Okay, that's new.
他动不了
He can't move.
他们在同时使用超能力
They're using their powers at the same time.
-我们该怎么办  -他不能穿过去什么的吗
- What are we gonna do? - Can't he phase or something?
这对那些家伙没有用
That doesn't work on these guys.
什么会有用
Well, what will?
把你手上的东西给我
Give me that thing in your hands.
另一个
The other thing.
这才更有道理
That makes more sense.
我可以调整这玩意以便模拟
I can rejigger this to mimic the resonance fields
斯卡德端口的共振力场
from Scudder's portals, make it so
好让巴里能操控那些镜子
Barry can manipulate the mirrors.
那尖峰人怎么办
But what about Top?
这也能还原
This will also restore
她造成的那些稀薄效应
whatever rarefaction effect she's causing.
好  太好了  真机智
Yes, that's good. That's brilliant.
但是打不开新的缺口
But without opening another breach,
我们怎么能够把它及时送到他手上
how can we possibly get it into his hands in time?
我带去给他
I'll take it to him.
我从时间穹顶看到你们在忙什么了
I saw what you were doing from the time vault.
你们需要帮忙
You need help.
给我吧
Give it to me.
去吧
Go.
是时候该我做些什么了
Thought it was about time I did something.
西斯科做的
Cisco made it.
现在她的超能力影响不了我们了
Now her powers won't affect us.
他去哪  我们就能去哪
We can go anywhere he does.
现在胜算几率一样了吧
The odds seem pretty even now, huh?
走
Go.
快走
不介意吧
You mind?
您请便
Be my guest.
抓到你了
Gotcha.
在一次奇怪的打斗中  近年来首次
In a bizarre twist, and the first sighting in years,
[突发新闻]
极速者搭档挫败犯罪分子
有人见到两名红色极速者
eyewitnesses claim not one but two Scarlet Speedsters
共同出力逮捕了山姆·斯卡德
were responsible for apprehending Sam Scudder
以及罗莎琳德·狄伦
and Rosalind Dillon,
即镜像大师和尖峰人
AKA Mirror Master and Top.
我想我下面要说的话也正是
I'm sure I speak for all residents of Central City
中城市民的心声
when I say this:
闪电侠  如果你有在收看
Flash, if you're watching,
很高兴你能回归
it's good to see you again.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
-闪电侠队回归了  -是啊
- Team Flash, back at it again.- Yeah.
我觉得这是个好开端  西斯科
Yeah, I think this was a good first step, Cisco,
但我们还有很长的路要走
but yeah, we have a ways to go.
尤其是我
Especially me.
我听见你说的了
I heard what you said.
你是对的
And you were right.
爱瑞丝不会希望如此
Iris wouldn't have wanted this.
她希望我们能像一家人一样
She would have wanted us to stay a family.
我破坏了这个与她的约定
I broke that promise to her--
也破坏了和你们的约定
to all of you.
你让我明白  即使萨维塔不在了
You made me realize, even though Savitar's gone,
我还是会让他得逞
I've--I've still been letting him win.
我错了
I was wrong to do that.
如果你们愿意再成为一家人
If you're all willing to... try to be a family again...
我觉得我也可以
I think I can, too.
我不知道该
I don't know which--
该先拥抱谁
which one of you to hug first.
他
Him.
我不知道你怎么看  但也算我一个
Well, I don't know about you, but...I'm in.
HR  你呢
H.R.? What do you say?
我还有好多咖啡要品尝
Yeah, I got a lot of coffee tastings
很多书要看...
and some book readings--
还有好多美女等着撩
lot of women left to charm,
但也算上我
but I--I'm in.
你知道吗
You know what?
大伙可以在HR的吉特咖啡店免费畅饮咖啡
Free coffees for the gang at H.R. Jitters.
也许还是九折吧  我请  我们走
Maybe 10% off. On me, let's go.
谢谢
Thank you.
-谢谢  -我知道这一定很难
- Thank you. - I know how hard this must be.
不  你并不知道
No, you don't.
现在还不会知道
Not yet.
这就是问题所在
That's the problem.
我们都没法改变即将发生的事
And neither of us can change what's gonna happen.
我希望我能帮上你的忙  相信我  真的
I wish I could help you, believe me, I do.
但你把萨维塔困在了神速力中
But you trapped Savitar in the Speed Force.
告诉我你是怎么办到的
Just tell me how you did it.
有人帮我
I had help.
-谁帮你的  -一个物理学家
- Help from who? - A physicist.
她叫特蕾西·布兰德
Her name's Tracy Brand.
她为我创造了这个神速力陷阱
She made the Speed Force trap for me.
为什么你之前没有告诉我
Why wouldn't you tell me this before?
因为她四年前才研究出
Because she didn't figure out the technology
这个技术
until four years ago.
爱瑞丝死后四年
Four years after Iris died.
等下
Hang on.
我不知道她在哪儿
I don't know where she is.
我一点儿也不懂这上面的东西
And I don't understand anything that's on here.
但上面有她的所有资料
But that's got all her information on it.
也许你回去的时候  你能找到她...
Maybe when you go back, you can find her and...
我不知道  她能为你解密
I don't know, she can decipher it for you.
希望如此
I hope so.
但如果不行...
But if not...
多留些和爱瑞丝的美好回忆
Just make some good memories with Iris.
尽全力把这些回忆牢记心间
Hold onto 'em as tight as you can.
祝你好运
Good luck.
奇怪  感觉就像《回到未来》中的那样
Weird, it feels just like "Back to the Future."
那么我就是布朗博士
Which would make me Doc Brown.
你不会给我写什么信吧
You're not gonna give me some kind of letter, are you?
不  我不会的
No, I will not.
我要做点什么纠正这些
I'm gonna do something to fix that.
你是一个超棒的超级英雄  不能失去超能力
You're too good of a superhero to lose those powers.
你知道你是我的死党吧
You know you're my BFF, right?
你也是
You too, man.
等等  你有没有...
Whoa. Wait, did you--
起作用了吗  我们需要再试一次吗
Did it not work? Do we need to try again?
不用  去过回来了
No, I went. I'm back.
你回来了
You're back?
我去了未来
I went to the future.
多远
How far?
八年后
Eight years from now.
我需要和自己谈谈找出萨维塔是谁
I needed to talk to myself and find out who Savitar was.
找到了吗
Did you?
没有
No.
但是我找到条可以用的线索
But I got a lead. Something we can use.
会帮助我们阻止他
Something that'll help us stop him.
巴里  你有凯特琳的消息吗
Barry, did you learn anything about Caitlin?
她和萨维塔结盟了
She aligned herself with Savitar.
为什么她要这样
Why would she do that?
不知道
I don't know.
但是我们得
But we need to find her,
在永远失去她之前找到她
before she's lost to us forever.
好吧  我去中城警局
All right, I'll get to CCPD.
是  我们...
Yeah, and we'll, uh...
我们勇往直前  是吧
we'll dive in here, right?
是吧  队友们  闪电侠小队
Right, team? Team Flash.
数到三
On three.
好吧
Okay. Okay.
乔
Joe.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
-你还好吗  -还好  只是...
- You okay? - Yeah, I'm fine. I just...
只是想让你知道不管发生什么
I just want you to know that no matter what happens,
我会一直在你身边
I'm always gonna be there for you.
我知道  巴仔
I know that, Bar.
我知道
I know.
谢谢
Thank you.
刚才是怎么了
What was that about?
只是履行给你的诺言
I'm just keeping that promise I made to you.
闪电侠
我在等你
I've been waiting for you.
不要怕  我的孩子
Fear not, my child.
我只是来给你想要的
I have come only to offer you what you desire.
那是什么呢
And what's that?
救赎
Selvation.
你想治愈我
You want to cure me?
把我变回凯特琳·斯诺
Turn me back to Caitlin Snow
不
No.
我会确保
I'm gonna make sure
凯特琳永远不回来
Caitlin never returns.
为什么我要相信你
Why should I trust you?
你要我做什么
What do you need me to do?